A Guide to the University Press of Virginia, General Office Files, ca. 1960-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University Press of Virginia, General Office Files ca. 1960-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-24/1/2.881
This collection consists of ca. 600 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the University Press of Virginia, April 25, 1988.
Scope and Content
General office files including correspondence with other presses.
Contents List
- "A" 1964-1977 (Box-folder 1:1)
- Richard Abel and Co., Inc., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 1:2)
- "B" 1963-1979 (Box-folder 1:3)
- Bro-Dart, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1:4)
- "C" 1964-1976 (Box-folder 1:5)
- CEAA, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1:6)
- Cambridge University Press, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 1:7)
- Cornell University Press, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 1:8)
- "D" 1969-1976 (Box-folder 1:9)
- Duke University Press, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 1:10)
- "E" 1966-1975 (Box-folder 1:11)
- "F" 1964-1978 (Box-folder 1:12)
- Feffer and Simons, 1964-1975 (Box-folder 1:13)
- Ford Foundation, 1965 (Box-folder 1:14)
- "G" 1964-1974 (Box-folder 1:15)
- "H" 1964-1978 (Box-folder 1:16)
- Harvard University Press, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 1:17)
- Holt, Rinehart and Winston, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 1:18)
- "I-J" 1963-1978 (Box-folder 2:1)
- IBM Typewriter, 1972 (Folder 2:2)
- Import Data Sheet, n.d. (Box-folder 2:3)
- "K" 1966-1976 (Box-folder 2:4)
- "L" 1968-1975 (Box-folder 2:5)
- "M" 1964-1978 (Box-folder 2:6)
- McGrath Publishing Company, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 2:7)
- "N" 1963-1976 (Box-folder 2:8)
- "O" 1965-1976 (Box-folder 2:9)
- "P-Q" 1966-1977 (Box-folder 2:10)
- Phi Beta Kappa- Const. Revision Committee, 1970 (Box-folder 2:11)
- "R" 1965-1979 (Box-folder 2:12)
- Reader Reports from Other Presses, n.d. (Box-folder 2:13)
- Royal Copier, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2:14)
- "S" 1967-1978 (Box-folder 3:1)
- "T" 1967-1975 (Box-folder 3:2)
- "U" 1969-1973 (Box-folder 3:3)
- University Press of New England, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3:4)
- University Presses: A-G, 1967-1976 (Box-folder 3:5)
- University Presses: H-M, 1964-1977 (Box-folder 3:6)
- University Presses: N-R, 1964-1973 (Box-folder 3:7)
- University Presses: S-Z, 1966-1978 (Box-folder 3:8)
- "V" 1966-1974 (Box-folder 3:9)
- Virginia-Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 3:10)
- "W" 1963-1976 (Box-folder 3:11)
- Xerox Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 3:12)
- "X-Y-Z" 1970-1972 (Box-folder 3:13)